<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<messages>
    <lang code="en">
        <ABOUT>
            A service that is another revival of the 
            YouTube application for the Nintendo Wii.
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• Better video quality
• Less crashes on video playback and pairing
• Play videos of any duration with NO limits.
• As you browse, more videos will be loaded per page with pagination supported.
• Captions / Subtitles are available
• Videos might take a while to load, if the channel skips to a new video, 
  wait for a couple seconds or minutes, then try going back to a previous
  one you have selected.
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           author by RedFire,
              "Invidious" 
           author by Omar Roth,
               "YouTube" 
           author by Google,
               "YouTube"
           Wii version licensed by
               Nintendo,
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           author by Nintendo,
           Helpers:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           Video codec info by
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     Requirements:
       • A computer or a device that allows you to 
         copy and place contents on your SD card as 
         long as it's formatted to FAT32.
       • A modded Nintendo Wii or Wii U (vWii)
         You can use Dolphin, but that's not the best option
         as YouTube channel's Flash player displayed on 
         screen is laggy.
       • Click on the 'Download' button to download 
         the WAD.
       • Get your SD card, copy the WAD you just 
         downloaded and place it on your 
         SD card, either in the "wads" folder 
         or somewhere.
       • Install the WAD with a WAD manager on 
         your Wii or Wii U (vWii)
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
    <lang code="es">
        <ABOUT>
            Un servicio que supone otro relanzamiento de la 
            aplicación de YouTube para la Nintendo Wii.
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• Mejor calidad de video
• Menos fallos en la reproducción de videos y emparejamiento
• Reproducir videos de cualquier duración sin límites.
• A medida que navegas, se cargarán más videos por página con paginación.
• Subtítulos / Closed Captions disponibles
• Es posible que los videos tarden un poco en cargarse. 
  Si el canal cambia a un video nuevo, espera unos 
  segundos o minutos y luego intenta volver al video 
  anterior que habías seleccionado.
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           autor por RedFire,

              "Invidious" 
           autor por Omar Roth,
          
               "YouTube" 
           autor por Google,
           
               "YouTube"
           Versión de Wii con licencia de
               Nintendo,
               
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           autor por Nintendo,
           
           Ayudantes:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           
           Información del códec de video 
           proporcionada por
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     Requisitos:
       • Una computadora o un dispositivo que le permita 
         copiar y colocar contenidos en su tarjeta SD 
         siempre que esté formateada a FAT32.

       • Una Wii o Wii U (vWii) modificada
         Puede usar Dolphin, pero no es la mejor opción 
         ya que el reproductor Flash del canal de YouTube 
         se ve lento.

       • Haga clic en el botón 'Descargar' para descargar 
         el WAD.

       • Tome su tarjeta SD, copie el WAD que acaba de 
         descargar y colóquelo en su 
         tarjeta SD, ya sea en la carpeta "wads" 
         o en otra ubicación.

       • Instale el WAD con un administrador de WAD en 
         su Wii o Wii U (vWii)
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
    <lang code="fr">
        <ABOUT>
            Il s'agit d'un service qui constitue une nouvelle 
            version de l'application YouTube pour la console 
            Nintendo Wii.
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• Meilleure qualité vidéo
• Moins de plantages lors de la lecture et de l'appairage
• Lire des vidéos de toute durée sans limites.
• Plus de vidéos seront chargées par page avec pagination.
• Sous-titres disponibles
• Le chargement des vidéos peut prendre un certain temps. 
  Si la chaîne passe à une nouvelle vidéo, attendez 
  quelques secondes ou minutes, puis essayez de revenir 
  à la vidéo précédente que vous aviez sélectionnée.
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           auteur RedFire,
           
              "Invidious" 
           auteur Omar Roth,
          
               "YouTube" 
           auteur Google,
           
               "YouTube"
           Version Wii sous licence de
               Nintendo,
               
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           auteur Nintendo,
           
           Aide:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           
           Informations sur le codec vidéo par
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     Exigences :
       • Un ordinateur ou un appareil vous permettant de 
         copier et placer le contenu sur votre carte SD 
         tant qu'elle est formatée en FAT32.

       • Une Wii ou Wii U (vWii) modifiée
         Vous pouvez utiliser Dolphin, mais ce n’est pas la meilleure option 
         car le lecteur Flash de la chaîne YouTube 
         est lent à l’écran.

       • Cliquez sur le bouton 'Télécharger' pour télécharger 
         le WAD.

       • Prenez votre carte SD, copiez le WAD que vous venez de 
         télécharger et placez-le sur votre 
         carte SD, soit dans le dossier "wads" 
         ou ailleurs.

       • Installez le WAD avec un gestionnaire de WAD sur 
         votre Wii ou Wii U (vWii)
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
    <lang code="it">
        <ABOUT>
            Un servizio che rappresenta un'ulteriore 
            riproposizione dell'applicazione YouTube per 
            Nintendo Wii.
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• Migliore qualità video
• Meno crash durante la riproduzione e l'accoppiamento
• Riproduzione di video di qualsiasi durata senza limiti.
• Più video caricati per pagina con paginazione.
• Sottotitoli disponibili
• Il caricamento dei video potrebbe richiedere del tempo. 
  se il canale passa a un nuovo video, attendete qualche 
  secondo o minuto, quindi provate a tornare al video 
  precedente che avevate selezionato.
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           autore RedFire,
           
              "Invidious" 
           autore Omar Roth,
          
               "YouTube" 
           autore Google,
           
               "YouTube"
           Versione Wii con licenza di
               Nintendo,
               
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           autore Nintendo,
           
           Aiutanti:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           
           Informazioni sul codec video fornite da
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     Requisiti:
       • Un computer o un dispositivo che consenta di 
         copiare e posizionare i contenuti sulla scheda SD 
         purché sia formattata in FAT32.

       • Una Wii o Wii U (vWii) modificata
         Puoi usare Dolphin, ma non è l'opzione migliore 
         perché il lettore Flash del canale YouTube 
         è lento sullo schermo.

       • Clicca sul pulsante 'Download' per scaricare 
         il WAD.

       • Prendi la tua scheda SD, copia il WAD appena 
         scaricato e posizionalo sulla tua 
         scheda SD, nella cartella "wads" 
         o altrove.

       • Installa il WAD con un gestore WAD sulla 
         tua Wii o Wii U (vWii)
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
    <lang code="de">
        <ABOUT>
            Ein Dienst, der eine weitere Neuauflage der YouTube-
            Anwendung für die Nintendo Wii darstellt.
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• Bessere Videoqualität
• Weniger Abstürze bei Wiedergabe und Kopplung
• Videos beliebiger Länge abspielbar ohne Limits.
• Mehr Videos pro Seite mit Pagination geladen.
• Untertitel verfügbar
• Das Laden der Videos kann etwas dauern. Falls 
  der Kanal zu einem neuen Video wechselt, warten 
  Sie ein paar Sekunden oder Minuten und versuchen 
  Sie dann, zu einem zuvor ausgewählten Video 
  zurückzukehren.
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           Autor RedFire,
           
              "Invidious" 
           Autor Omar Roth,
          
               "YouTube" 
           Autor Google,
           
               "YouTube"
           Wii-Version lizenziert von
               Nintendo,
               
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           Autor Nintendo,
           
           Helfer:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           
           Video-Codec-Infos von
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     Anforderungen:
       • Ein Computer oder Gerät, das es Ihnen erlaubt, 
         Inhalte auf Ihre SD-Karte zu kopieren und abzulegen, 
         solange sie im FAT32-Format ist.

       • Eine modifizierte Nintendo Wii oder Wii U (vWii)
         Sie können Dolphin verwenden, aber das ist nicht die beste Option, 
         da der Flash-Player des YouTube-Kanals 
         auf dem Bildschirm langsam ist.

       • Klicken Sie auf die Schaltfläche 'Download', um 
         das WAD herunterzuladen.

       • Nehmen Sie Ihre SD-Karte, kopieren Sie das WAD, das Sie gerade 
         heruntergeladen haben, und legen Sie es auf Ihrer 
         SD-Karte ab, entweder im "wads"-Ordner 
         oder anderswo.

       • Installieren Sie das WAD mit einem WAD-Manager auf 
         Ihrer Wii oder Wii U (vWii)
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
    <lang code="nl">
        <ABOUT>
            Een dienst die een nieuwe versie is van de YouTube-
            applicatie voor de Nintendo Wii.
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• Betere videokwaliteit
• Minder crashes bij video afspelen en koppelen
• Video's van elke duur afspelen zonder limieten.
• Meer video's per pagina geladen met paginatie.
• Ondertiteling beschikbaar
• Het laden van video's kan even duren. Als het 
  kanaal overschakelt naar een nieuwe video, wacht 
  dan een paar seconden of minuten en probeer 
  vervolgens terug te gaan naar de vorige
  video die je had geselecteerd.
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           auteur RedFire,
           
              "Invidious" 
           auteur Omar Roth,
          
               "YouTube" 
           auteur Google,
           
               "YouTube"
           Wii-versie gelicentieerd door
               Nintendo,
               
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           auteur Nintendo,
           
           Hulp:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           
           Video codec info door
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     Vereisten:
       • Een computer of apparaat waarmee u 
         inhoud op uw SD-kaart kunt kopiëren en plaatsen, 
         zolang deze is geformatteerd in FAT32.

       • Een gemodificeerde Nintendo Wii of Wii U (vWii)
         U kunt Dolphin gebruiken, maar dat is niet de beste optie, 
         omdat de Flash-speler van het YouTube-kanaal 
         op het scherm traag is.

       • Klik op de knop 'Download' om 
         het WAD te downloaden.

       • Pak uw SD-kaart, kopieer het WAD dat u zojuist 
         hebt gedownload en plaats het op uw 
         SD-kaart, in de "wads"-map 
         of ergens anders.

       • Installeer het WAD met een WAD-manager op 
         uw Wii of Wii U (vWii)
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
    <lang code="ja">
        <ABOUT>
            これは、ニンテンドーWii向けYouTubeアプリケーシ
            ョンのもう一つの復活版となるサービスです。
        </ABOUT>
        <STATUS>
• ビデオ品質の向上
• ビデオ再生およびペアリングのクラッシュが減少
• 長さに関係なく動画を再生可能
• ページをスクロールすると、ページごとにさらに動画が読み込まれます（ページネーション対応）
• 字幕 / サブタイトル対応
• 動画の読み込みには時間がかかる場合があります。チャンネルが次の動画に切り替わった
  場合は、数秒または数分待ってから、以前に選択した動画に戻ってみてください。
        </STATUS>
        <CREDITS>
              "Liinback"
           作者 RedFire,
           
              "Invidious" 
           作者 Omar Roth,
          
               "YouTube" 
           作者 Google,
           
               "YouTube"
           Wiiバージョンライセンス提供
               Nintendo,
               
            "Nintendo Wii" 
           作者 Nintendo,
           
           ヘルパー:
            ftde0
			SMG
            ljcool2006,
           
           ビデオコーデック情報提供
           SuperrSonic &amp; Wikipedia
        </CREDITS>
        <GUIDE>
                     必要条件:
       • コンピュータまたはSDカードに内容をコピーして配置できるデバイス 
         （FAT32でフォーマットされていること）。

       • 改造済みのNintendo Wii または Wii U (vWii)
         Dolphinを使用できますが、YouTubeチャンネルのFlashプレーヤーは 
         画面上で遅く表示されるため最適ではありません。

       • 「Download」ボタンをクリックして 
         WADをダウンロードします。

       • SDカードを取り、ダウンロードしたWADを 
         SDカードにコピーします。
         「wads」フォルダまたは任意の場所に置きます。

       • WiiまたはWii U (vWii)にWADマネージャーでWADをインストールします。
        </GUIDE>
    </lang>
</messages>
